Prerna Kangtani

I'm a seasoned web developer in creating user-friendly and visually appealing websites. I specialize in utilizing HTML, CSS, JavaScript, php,React, NodeJs and Next JS 14 to craft cutting-edge solutions that exceed client expectations and drive online success.

Contact

2/32 Bohra Market, Ichalkaranji 8767322683 prean14012003@gmail.com https://prerna-portfolioseven.vercel.app/

Work Experience

Web Developer, TF Strategies Pvt. Ltd.

Jan 2024 - Present

- Introduced with Next JS 14, implemented nodejs server engine to make static and dynamic website.
- Added payment gateways and database to make website dynamic.
 Used MongoDB and MySQL for database. For payment gateway I used
 Razorpay
- Connected with clients, discussed designs for website implemented in Figma and then developed accordingly using next js (used nodejs also), or php.

Web Developer, Acmegrade

Jun 2023 - Aug 2023

- Internship training program learned to make websites using HTML, CSS, Javascript, php
- Used Database to store users credentials using MySQL and xampp.
- Made e-commerce project Furni where all teachings have been implemented.

Research Associate, Ameliorate Digital Consultancy Pvt. Ltd.

Sep 2022 - May 2023

- · Learned how SEO works and made content accordingly.
- Used Quilbot to make content unique, Google Trends to work on particular keywords that will rank.
- Made several research for seveal markets and made overall report which can be helpful for companies working in that specific market; using Excel, Word and Powerpoint.

Skills

Technical Skills

- · NextJs, ReactJs
- NodeJs, ExpressJs
- HTML, CSS
- · MongoDB, MySQL
- JavaScript, php
- Figma
- C, C++
- Datastructures, OOPs

Languages

- English (Fluent)
- · Hindi (Fluent)

Certification/Short Courses

- Web and Mobile Designer UI UX
- Data Structures using C and C++
- Advance in Excel
- · Professional and Life Skills

Educational Background

Bachelor of Computer Application

Amity University Online Sep 2021 - July 2024

- · Project on "Automation of Research Report". using Java OOP
- · Got certifications in Advanced Excel, Professional and Life Skills